<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Internal Red Tape Reduction Report</title>
    <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Internal Red Tape Reduction Report</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 3: A service strategy for internal services</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-3/</guid>
      <description>The findings from the Internal Red Tape Reduction initiative highlight poor client service as a major irritant for many public servants in their day-to-day work lives. Public servants told us that they experienced the following when accessing internal services:
 Client must initiate contact Lack of support and guidance Conflicting or unreliable advice Local expertise ignored Multiple contacts/ a &amp;ldquo;not my job&amp;rdquo; mentality  The Internal Red Tape findings underscore the importance of focusing service excellence on internal services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 2: Snapshots of internal red tape stories</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-2/</guid>
      <description>Snapshot of your Internal Red Tape Stories  Hide image     Snapshot: Getting IT help Requesting IT support is a task that most employees undertake from time to time. Employees&amp;rsquo; stories about getting IT help range from relatively straightforward requests, such as setting up a dual monitor, to those that are more complex, like obtaining access to a closed network.
Two central themes emerge from these stories: the challenges inherent in transitioning from locally-based to centralized services, and the ambiguity around roles and responsibilities that sometimes results from these transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 1: How the project was done</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-1/</guid>
      <description>Unravelling red rape with design-thinking The methodology of the internal red tape reduction project was centred around using design-thinking principles in order to have user experiences to help departments across the federal public service solve red tape issues being encountered in their day-to-day jobs. In recent years, governments around the world have been turning to design-thinking to simplify burdensome processes, prototype solutions and engage public servants and citizens to bring change to large-scale complex systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4: Achievements and reflections</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>The work of the Tiger Team is also a story of discovery. The Tiger Team adopted new approaches and new tools to identify problems and design solutions. Through social media and in-person dialogue, as well as surveys, the team journeyed with public servants across the country to unravel internal red tape. At times, the work seemed daunting, as the team had to manage the demand for quick and definitive outcomes when the issues still seemed nebulous and the project deadline was fast approaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3: Exposing the root causes of the irritants</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>In brief Enabling interdepartmental collaboration In Phase II, TBS established interdepartmental working groups comprised of both “rule makers” and “rule followers” to perform a deep dive into three areas: procurement, staffing, and internal processes for grants and contributions.
To mark the launch of Phase II and serve as a first step toward addressing the key findings of Phase I, the Tiger Team held a one-day forum that brought together 72 participants from 26 departments, all working on projects related to these areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2: Unravelling internal red tape, one story at a time</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>In brief Engaging public servants at the working level A key element of the Engagement Phase was to listen to public servants at the working level about their encounters with internal red tape in order to identify common irritants. A variety of engagement channels were used to reach as many public servants as possible, in departments and agencies, communities of practice and networks. The Tiger Team sparked discussions online through blogs and discussion groups on the Government’s social media platform, GCconnex, under the group Blueprint 2020 – Reducing Internal Red Tape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1: A call to action</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>In June 2013, Blueprint 2020 (BP2020) was launched, setting in motion an unprecedented engagement exercise with public servants about the future of the public service of Canada, with “the goal of ensuring that it remains a world class institution.” During the dialogue that took place in the weeks following the launch of BP2020, public servants reported that…
 “Many rules and processes are overly complex, top-down, siloed, and lack coherence and consistency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>