<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Internal Red Tape Reduction Report</title>
    <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Internal Red Tape Reduction Report</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 14:41:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Report</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 14:41:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/all/</guid>
      <description>During the Government of Canada’s Blueprint 2020 discussions, public servants reported that many rules and processes were overly complex, top-down and lacked coherence. Simplifying internal processes and reducing internal red tape was identified as one of the five priority areas of action in Destination 2020. This report presents key findings and recommendations that reflect the voices of public servants. Released under the Access to Information Act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 3: A service strategy for internal services</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-3/</guid>
      <description>The findings from the Internal Red Tape Reduction initiative highlight poor client service as a major irritant for many public servants in their day-to-day work lives. A Service Strategy for Internal Services would guide the adoption of service excellence in internal services, and help to anchor it in the day-to-day culture of the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 2: Snapshots of internal red tape stories</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-2/</guid>
      <description>Snapshots of internal red tape stories from public servants in the Government of Canada, including: Getting IT help, The trouble with travel, Evaluating performance, Changing departments, Security clearance screening, Navigating myKEY, and Accessing systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 1: How the project was done</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/annex-1/</guid>
      <description>The methodology of the internal red tape reduction project was centred around using design-thinking principles in order to have user experiences to help departments across the federal public service solve red tape issues being encountered in their day-to-day jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4: Achievements and reflections</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>The Tiger Team adopted new approaches and new tools to identify problems and design solutions. Through social media and in-person dialogue, as well as surveys, the team journeyed with public servants across the country to unravel internal red tape. Along the way, commonly held assumptions were challenged and new insights were gained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3: Exposing the root causes of the irritants</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>In Phase II, TBS established interdepartmental working groups comprised of both “rule makers” and “rule followers” to perform a deep dive into three areas: procurement, staffing, and internal processes for grants and contributions. Working Group participants were able to expose the root causes of internal red tape in each area and design possible solutions to move forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2: Unravelling internal red tape, one story at a time</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>A key element of the Engagement Phase was to listen to public servants at the working level about their encounters with internal red tape in order to identify common irritants. A variety of engagement channels were used to reach as many public servants as possible, in departments and agencies, communities of practice and networks. Through these efforts, the Tiger Team reached more than 2,000 public servants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1: A call to action</title>
      <link>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://internal-red-tape-reduction-report.github.io/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>In June 2013, Blueprint 2020 was launched, setting in motion an unprecedented engagement exercise with public servants about the future of the public service of Canada, with “the goal of ensuring that it remains a world class institution.” A small multi-disciplinary Tiger Team to engage public servants using social media and roundtables to identify “some of the biggest specific irritants.”</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>